Lady Livia, did- did you misspeak?
I am perfectly clear.
Step aside.
I will handle this myself.
Years ago, I
got engaged to Severin.
Back then he was
ambitious and full of
promise, everything a
noble lady could want.
But he changed.
When Count Carter sent him
away to gain experience,
he just hid in the mines,
wasting his days with commoners.
Count Carter gave up on him.
So did I.
That’s why Redmond
became the rightful heir.
Today,
I am ending my engagement to Severin Carter
and marrying Redmond instead.
I trust you can
all understand my painful decision.
Livia, I stand with you!
Livia, the gods have
finally opened your eyes.
A woman of
your noble standing could
never be with trash like Severin.
Severin Carter, do you
have anything left to say?